{
  "title": "Compound words: someone, anyone, somewhere",
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "I asked if ........ wanted an ice cream? ",
      "answers": ["anyone", "someone", "everyone", "no one"],
      "correct": "anyone"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "Did ........ phone me when I was out?",
      "answers": ["anyone", "someone", "everyone", "no one"],
      "correct": "anyone"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "You're face looks horribly familiar. Haven't I seen you ........ before?",
      "answers": ["anywhere ", "nowhere", "somewhere", "everywhere"],
      "correct": "somewhere"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "She left the room without saying ........",
      "answers": ["nothing", "something", "everything", "anything"],
      "correct": "anything"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "I have never been ........ more beautiful than Thailand.",
      "answers": ["anywhere ", "nowhere", "somewhere", "everywhere"],
      "correct": "anywhere"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "Who was at the party? ......... Pete, Anne. Mark, Barry, all the Pearsonâ€™s, Sally Masters and Sally Bennett.",
      "answers": ["anyone", "someone", "everyone", "no one"],
      "correct": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What would you like to eat for lunch? ......... I don't mind",
      "answers": ["nothing", "something", "everything", "anything"],
      "correct": "anything"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "Where do you want to go on holiday? ........ with a  I don't care where we go a; long as it's sunny and beach has got a nice sandy beach.",
      "answers": ["anywhere ", "nowhere", "somewhere", "everywhere"],
      "correct": "anywhere"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "I have ........ to say to you. Goodbye.",
      "answers": ["nothing", "something", "everything", "anything"],
      "correct": "nothing"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "I felt so embarrassed. I was sure that ........ was looking at me.",
      "answers": ["anyone", "someone", "everyone", "no one"],
      "correct": "everyone"
    }
  ]
}
